All right, you're done. Let's talk about how I
solved this one. First, let's take all our code, and
copy it from the fetch weather task. The intent
service actually creates a helper thread for us to run
on. Similar to what async task does. So we
can just copy this stuff from doing background to on
handle intent. Let's add a few helpful constants, such as
log tag and an Intent Extra, so we can pass
in the location query. Now, we're just going to
go through and clean up some of the errors.
After all, Intent Service doesn't return a value. And
since it's a service, it has its own context.
And that's it. We've turned out fetch weather task
into an intents service, pretty straightforward. Now we just
need to call it. So, now in the update
weather function from within forecast fragment, we can call
the service using an explicit intent,
putting the parameter into an intent extra.
All right, let's take a look at how that runs. And when we
hit the refresh button, it'll use our new service. Pretty nice. And we
really can't tell any difference, which is how we'd expect things to be.